Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology Alumni Association records, [ca. 1928-2010].
New York State College of Human Ecology Alumni Association records
- June 1981-May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Committee Reports
    - History Archives, September 18, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Admissions Committee, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Legislative Committee, September 8, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Long Range Committee, October 20, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Association Membership, April 30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Resource Program, April 30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Association Student Activities fund, April 30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Nominating Committee, March 11, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Continuing Education, September 30, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Career issues letter, January 20, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- June 1982-May 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors & Officers (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committee Chairs (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 11, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee, June 11, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board, June 11, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board, September 25, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board, February 12, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - December 31, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Various Committee Records, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Budget, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committee Reports (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Letters (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Milestones in History (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Human Ecology Alumni in New York State (Box 1, Folder 24)
- June 1983-May 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors & Officers (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Committee Chairs & Members (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 10, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board, June 10, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board, October 15, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Various Committee Records, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Executive Board, January 21, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board, April 14, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - December 31, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Committee Reports (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Constitution Revision, June 18, 1983
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - College Banner, February 17, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- June 1984-May 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 8, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board, June 8, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board, September 28, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board, September 29, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board, October 27, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board, February 2, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Executive committee, June 23, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Letter to Executive Board, December 19, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - December 31, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Committee Reports (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Membership letter (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Various Committee Records, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Honors and Recognition Committee Records, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- June 1985-May 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Committee Chairs & Members (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 14, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Executive Board, June 14, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Executive Board, February 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - December 31, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - December 31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Treasurer's report, April 1 - June 30, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Various Committee Records, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cumulative quarter expense sheet, January 1 - June 20, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Cumulative expenses, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Committee reports (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Report from Director of Alumni Affairs (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Breakfast program (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Notes on Class of 1935 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- June 1986-May 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors booklet (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Committee Chairs (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 13, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Executive Board, June 13, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Executive Board, September 27, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Executive Board, February 7, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Executive Board, April 4, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Budget, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer's report, July 1 - September 30, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer's report, October 1 - December 31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - March 31, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer's report, April 1 - June 30, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cumulative expenses, January 1 - March 31, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cumulative expenses, April 1 - June 30, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Accounting procedures (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Budget worksheet (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Expense approval from (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hum Ec. alum in major cities, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Committee reports (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Long range planning (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Notes on Class of '26 & '36 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - HEAA calendar of events, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Giving record by area, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Various Commmittee Records, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors Guide, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- June 1987-May 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Committee Chairs & Members (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Association Board as of January 1, 1988
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 12, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Executive Board, June 12, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Executive Board, August 6, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Executive Board, September 19, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Executive Board, January 29-30, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Executive Board, April 6, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Budget, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Treasurer's report, July 1 - September 30, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Treasurer's report, October 1 - December 31, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - December 31, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Committee reports (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Notes on Class of 1926 & 1936 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Various Committee Records, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- June 1988-May 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Committee Chairs (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 10, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Board of Directors, June 10, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Board of Directors, September 24, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Board of Directors, April 8, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Budget, January 5, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Asset statement (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Budget review, 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Committee reports (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - List of Presidents (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - List of Distinguished Teacher award (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - List of recipients of Helen Bull Vandervort (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Helen Bull Vandervort Award, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - List of Dean's Award (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Calender of events, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Proposed student activities, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Listing of HEAA officers, 1928-1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Scholarship applications and awards, 1930-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Alumni newsletter history and listing, 1939-1951 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Occupational bulletins (Nos. 8-39) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- HEAA, 1925-1939 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - HEAA newsletter, December 5, 1925 - December 9, 1939
  - Correspondence, June 1, 1926
  - Correspondence, May 31, 1927
  - Correspondence re: historical reference to HEAA, July 18, 1928
- HEAA newsletter, January 17, 1940 - December 20, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- HEAA newsletter, January 20, 1945 - December 15, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- HEAA newsletter, January 16, 1950 - November 15, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- HEAA newsletter, January 15, 1955 - November 15, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- HEAA newsletter, February 1, 1960 - November 16, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- HEAA newsletter, January 1965 - November 1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- HEAA newslatter, January 1970 - May 1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Bernice Hopkins Historical File, Created 1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- HEAA Board of Directors Guide, June 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Scholarship Committee, 1940s - 1960s (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Flora Rose awards & seminar room, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Scholarships/grants/cash awards, 1930s - 1980s (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Honors & Recognitions committee, 1960s - 1980s (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Distinguished teaching awards, 1979 and 1980s (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Organization of HEAA & HEAA newsletter, 1920s, 1960s, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 7)
- History & Archives committee, 1980s and 1990s (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Display case, 1970s - 1990s (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1917 Cornell women's pageant - letters about what was donated to the Archives, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Farm & Home alumni gathering, 1920s and 1930s (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Teas, receptions, 1930s and 1970s (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Institution Management - writing of the history, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous - newsletters from 1944, 1978, and 1980s, articles and some correspondence (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Human Ecology Alumni Association Handbook (Box 3, Folder 1)
- The College of Human Ecology Communications Study: Phase I - Alumni perceptions (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Human Ecology Alumni Association Board of Directors Guide (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Treasurer-Alumni Association Accounts, 1980-1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Handling of Financial Affairs and Special Allocations
  - Notes about the Treasury
  - Accounting Procedures
  - Expense Approval Form
  - Budget Worksheet
  - HEAA Budgets, 1981-1992
- Alumni Association Annual Reports, 1988-90 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Constitution and Bylaws Committee, 1984-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee Report, 1988-89
  - Revised Constitution and Bylaws, April 1990
  - Proposed Changes to the Constitution and Bylaws, January 19, 1987
  - Constitution and Bylaws, January 22, 1984
- Admissions Committee (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Committee Plan of Work, 1989-1990
  - Correspondence
- History and Archives Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Committee Plan of Work, 1990-1991, 1989-1990
  - Correspondence re: Microfilming of Human Ecology News, 1989
  - Correspondence
- Executive Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations Committee Correspondence
  - Minutes form the Board of Director's Meeting, June 9, 1989
  - HEAA Mission Statement and Long Range Plan, April 1989
  - HEAA's Dues Structure Analysis and Recommendations
  - Minutes from the Executive Committee Meeting, August 6, 1987
  - HEAA Board Committees, 1987-1988
  - Alumni Association Board, 1987-1988
- Development Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Development Committee Candidates
  - List of Scholarships and Grants, 1988-1989
  - New York State College of Human Ecology Undergraduate Financial Aid Funds, 1988
- Honors and Recognition Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Committee Plan of Work, 1989-1990
  - List of Members, 1988-1989
  - Distinguished Extension Award Information
  - Helen Bull Vandervort Alumni Achievement Award (HBVAAA) Information
  - Distinguished Service Award Information
  - Committee Plan of Work, 1988
  - HEAA Breakfast, June 12, 1987
  - Minutes from Meeting, June 12, 1987
  - Budget for the Honors and Recognition Committee, 1985-1986
- Helen Bull Vandervort Alumni Achievement Award (HBVAAA) History (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, 1968
  - Memo re: HBVAAA, 1988
  - Nominees, 1983
- HBVAAA, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- HBVAAA, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- HBVAAA, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - HBVAAA Nominations and Winners List, 1983-1990
  - Nominations, 1990
- Development Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Development Summary, 1975-1982
  - Potential Members, 1981
- Finance Committee, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Budget Worksheet, 1986
- Board of Directors By Term, 1982-1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - HEAA Board of Directors Lists
- History and Archives Committee (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Memos re: Allocation of College Funds to Records Management, 1986
  - Jamille Freed's Taped interview with David Knapp, July 1988
  - Report History and Archives Committee, April 1988
  - Oral History Interviewing, Life Cycle Format, Mary Rothschild
- Alumni Surveys (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Survey: Issues and Goals, 1985
  - Boston Area Alumni Survey, 1983
- Student Nominees for Alumni Association (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Student Activities Committee, HEAA Board of Directors Information on the Student Position
  - Blank Application
  - Nominees
- Alumni Association Job Descriptions (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Honors and Recognition Committee
  - Legislative Committee
  - Continuing Education Committee
  - Display Case Chairperson
- Alumni Career Panels (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Career Seminars
  - Correspondence re: Layered Fabrics for Use in Pesticide Protection Seminar
- Alumni Affairs - Events Sponsored, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Area Receptions
  - Topic Seminars
  - Symposiums and Luncheons with the Dean
  - Cornell Women's Seminars
- Alumni Affairs - Events Sponsored, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Women's Seminars
  - Newspaper Articles re: Cornell Women's Seminars
  - Women in Management Conference
  - Regional Conferences
- Alumni Affairs - Events Sponsored, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Portland Regional Meeting
  - Washington D.C. Regional Meeting
  - Seminars: Families in Contemporary America, Understanding Adolescents Understanding Themselves
- Campus Walks Boolket, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Information re: Martha Van Rensselar Hall
- Human Ecology Alumni Association: Committee Activities/Events: 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Helen Bull Vandervort Alumni Achievement Awards
  - Legislative Committee Report, 1984-1985
  - Minutes from Meeting, April 26, 1985
  - Nominees for the Board of Directors, 1986
  - HEAA Treasurer's Report, April 1, 1987 - June 30, 1987
  - Memo re: Government Affairs Reorganization
  - Honors and Recognition Committee Meeting, June 12, 1987
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, October 6, 1987
- Human Ecology Alumni Association Ecology Alumni Association Board of Directors Meeting/Committee Activities/Events, 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report, July 1988 - June 1989
  - Long Range Planning Committee Report, April 1989, February 1989
  - HEAA membership, October 1988 - January 1989
  - Homecoming Information, 1988
  - Annual Report, July 1978 - June 1988
  - Opportunities as Expressed in the Meetings with Deans or their Representatives on the Subject of Faculty/Alumni Interaction, August 10, 1987
  - Budget, 1988
  - Board Committees, 1987-1988
  - Long Range Planning Meeting, September 2, 1987
  - Special Events and Continuing Education Committee Meeting, January 29, 1988 October 5, 1987
- Board Meeting, April 15-16, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Committee Reports
  - HEAA Board Committees, 1987-1988
  - Special Events and Continuing Education Committee Meeting
  - HEAA Treasurer's Report
  - Asset Statement, March 27, 1988
  - HEAA Membership Statement
  - Minutes of the Meeting
- Committee Plans of Work, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Alumni Breakfast, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Program for HEAA Breakfast and Meeting, June 9, 1989
  - Breakfast Guidelines
  - Invitation to Faculty
  - List of Attendants
  - Breakfast Script
  - News and Notes of the Class of 1929 and 1939
- Alumni Breakfast Photographs, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Photo of Breakfast in MVR Auditorium
  - Photo of John Harding
  - Photo of Barbara Morse
  - Photo of Marcia Pimantel
- Alumni Seminars, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Memo re: Child Abuse Seminar
  - Information About the Computer Aided Design Studio Seminar
- Black Alumni Association Reunion, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Reception Invitation, June 10, 1989
  - Reunion Program Announcement
  - Contract with the Chris White Quartet, Entertainment
  - Tentative Cornell Black Alumni Association Reunion Schedule, 1989
- Board Meeting, April 8, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Minutes and Committee Reports
- Board Meetings, June 9, 1989 and October 6, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Human Ecology Update
  - Minutes from the Meeting
  - HEAA Board of Directors, 1989-1990
  - Mission Statement and Long Range Plan, April 1989
- Committee Plans of Work, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - List of Board CommitteeMembers, 1988-89
  - Interested Available Alumni for Board Committees
  - Committee Plans of Work
- Cornell Council - Dean's Luncheon, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Luncheon Program
  - Wine and Cheese Information
  - Information about the Luncheon
- Human Ecology Alumni Association Board of Directors: Activities/Committee Activities/Events, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Alumni Breakfast and 64th Annual Meeting
  - Claendar of Activities, 1989-90
  - Annual Report, July 1989 - June 30, 1990
  - HEAA Board of Directors Meeting, June 8, 1990
  - Budget, 1989
  - Handling of Financial Affairs and Special Allocations
  - Treasurer's Report, December 31, 1989
  - HEAA Senior Reception, 1989
  - Alumni-in-Residence Program
  - Alumni Career Services Committee Meeting, December 1989
  - Membership Reports
  - HEAA Annual Meeting, June 12, 1987
- Board Meeting, March 31, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Minutes of Meeting
  - Minutes, October 6, 1989
  - HEAA Budget, 1990
  - Treasurer's Report, December 31, 1989
  - Asset Statement, December 31, 1989
  - Membership Report, March 30, 1990
  - Constituion and Bylaws of the Alumni Association of the New York State College of Human Ecology
  - Long Range Planning Committee Report
  - Human Ecology News Survey Results, Fall 1989
  - Proposed Slate of Officers
- Board Meeting, June 8-9, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Minutes of the Meeting
  - List of HEAA Board of Directors, 1990-91
  - HEAA Membership Report, May 1990
  - Process for Development of Plan of work
  - Membership Report, May 31, 1990
  - Organizational Chart, May 1990
- Board Meeting, October 5, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Minutes of the Meeting
  - Goals, 1990-1991
  - Committees List
  - Minutes, June 8, 1990
  - Anniversary Gift Proposal
  - Committee Plan of Work Admissions, 1990-1991
- Committee Plans of Work, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Process for Development of Plan of Work
  - Human Ecology Board Committees, 1989-1990
  - Public Relations Plan of Work
- Committee Report and Committee Activities, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - The Alumni Association Board of Directors, 1990-1991
  - Membership Committee Report, February 1991
  - Proposed HEAA Committee Structure
  - Committee Reports, 1990-1991
- Human Ecology Board of Directors: Activities/Events, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Board of Directors, 1990
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991
  - Minutes, June 7, 1991
  - Dues Structure Analysis and Recommendations
  - Budget, 1990-1991
  - Asset Statement, 1991
- 65th Anniversary Institute-College of Human Ecology, October 6, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Program
  - Schedule of Events
  - Suggested Itinerary
  - Event Briefing
  - Operations Plan
  - Dean Firebaugh's Welcome to Anniversary Institute Attendees
- 65th Anniversary Institute - Photographs, October 1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Photographs and Contact Sheets
- Committee Reports and Committee Activities, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Annual and Special Events Committee Report, 1990-1991
  - The Evolution of Human Ecology Program
  - Honors and Recognition Committee Activity
  - Report to the Board of Directors
  - Capital Campaigns, June 6, 1991
  - Public Relations Committee
  - Nominees for the HEAA Board of Directors
  - Nominations and Elections Committee Information
  - HEAA Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, September 12, 1991 and October 10, 1992
- Human Ecology Alumni Association History and Constitution (Revised), 1991, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - HEAA: A Historical Perspective
  - Constitution and Bylaws of the Alumni Association of the New York State College of Human Ecology, rev., June 1991
- Human Ecology Alumni Association: Committee Activities/Events, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Alumni Update, October 11, 1991
  - 1991 Alumni-in Residence Program, October 20-22, 1991
  - Homecoming, 1991
  - Report on Homecoming Tailgate for HEAA
  - Federation Weekend Information, October 17-19, 1991
  - Cornell Campaign-Fundraising
  - Membership Report
  - Alumni Communications Survey
  - Adopt-A-Dean Campaign, 1991
  - The Alumni Association Board of Directors, 1991-1992
  - Alumni Breakfast and 65th Annual Meeting, June 8, 1991
- Human Ecology Alumni Association, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - HEAA Board Committees, 1991-1992
  - HEAA Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, February 1, 1992 and October 4, 1991
  - Summary of Development Tasks and Initiatives, June 17, 1992
  - Summary of Alumni Office Initatives, June 17, 1992
  - HEAA Annual Meeting, Juen 6, 1992
  - HEAA Annual Report, June 1991 - May 1992
  - Process for Development of Alumni Association Plan of Work and Budget
  - Budget Development Worksheet
  - HEAA Budget, September 1, 1991 - August 31, 1992
  - HEAA Treasurer's Report, August 31, 1991, November 31, 1991, May 30, 1992
  - HEAA Asset Statement, August 31, 1991, November 31, 1991
- Brochures and Publications, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Scholarhip-Alumni Association, 1950-1963 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Annual Reports, 1963, 1962, 1955, 1954, 1950
  - Summaries of Cash Awards
  - Applications for Cash Awards
- Occupational Bulletins, September 11, 1951 - May 11, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Home Economics Council (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Annual Meeting Report, May 1, 1953
  - Minutes, May 1, 1953
  - Research Projects in Process, 1952-1953
- Home Economics Alumni, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Land-Grant Centennial Celebration
  - Alumni Gathering in Kansas City, MO
- Iowa Alumni Curriculum Study (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence and Blank Survey
- Alumni Survey/ Conference on Progress (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Progress Report on Alumnae Survey
  - Conference on Home Economics, November 1, 1956
  - "What Do We Know About Our Degree-Holders?" - Report
- Home Economics Alumnae Teas, 1954-1958 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Alumni Institute, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Schedule
  - Food and Nutrition Seminar
  - "...Promises to Keep" Program
  - Early Bird Program
- Institution for Professional Home Economists, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Steering Committee
  - Program
  - Resume of Conference, May 17-18, 1957
- Home Economics Alumni Day, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence
- Remarks of Francis Keppel to New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers, Inc., April 25, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools - Questionnaire for Institutional Self-Evaluation (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Alumni Luncheons at American Home Economic Association Conventions (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence, 1955-1957
- Trustee Nominations, 1950s (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Alumni Trustee Nominations (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Blank Biographical Date File, Committee on Alumni Trustee Nominations (Box 3, Folder 67)
- HEAA 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Part I
    - Calendar of Events, 1992-1993
    - Board of Directors Booklet & Items